sleeter.com 2016-11-30

# Privacy Policy and Your Privacy Rights

                              Privacy Policy and Your Privacy Rights
                                               Last Updated March 1, 2015
General
This site is a service of Diversified Communications (“DIVERSIFIED”).
This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us using this web site or any other
DIVERSIFIED site (the “Site”). This Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected elsewhere, including
offline and on web sites linked to or from the Site.
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By using or accessing the Site, and/or by registering with the Site, you
agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use our Site or provide
any information to us.
In addition to reviewing this Privacy Policy, please also read our Terms of Use. Your use of our Site constitutes your
agreement to the Terms of Use.
We reserve the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will give you notice of the revised
Privacy Policy by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Site and by revising the “Last Updated” date at the top of
this Privacy Policy. You are responsible for regularly reviewing the current privacy policy. Any change, update or
modification we make will be effective immediately upon posting on our Site. Your continued access of our Site
after we post any changes or revisions constitutes your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy
Policy.
Your California Privacy Rights
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California customers to request certain information regarding our
disclosures of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. The law provides that we
may (1) respond to this request by proving certain information about our disclosures, or (2) if we maintain an
opt-out or opt-in procedure, by providing customers with a cost-free means to exercise that right.
To make such a request, please contact us at info@divcom.com, or the address below, and provide your name
and the address to which you would like us to respond.
Diversified Communications Attention:
Web Master/Privacy Rights
121 Free Street Portland,
ME 04101 USA
Collection of Information
We collect “automatic information” and “personally identifiable information.”
“Automatic information” is information automatically collected by our web server (which may be hosted by a
third-party) that your web browser makes available whenever you visit our Site, such as the IP address of your
computer, your operating system version and browser type, the duration of your visit to the Site, and other
standard tracking data we use to evaluate site traffic and usage patterns.
Most Diversified websites use "cookies," which are small text files stored on your device, to help operate the sites
and collect information about online activity. For instance, we use cookies to store your preferences and settings;
help with sign-in; provide targeted ads; combat fraud; and analyze site operations.
We also use web beacons to help deliver cookies, compile analytics and monitor behavior on websites. These may
include web beacons from third-party service providers.
                                                                           © 2015 Diversified Communications

At this time, we do not react to automated browser signals regarding tracking mechanisms, such as “do not track”
instructions. You have a variety of tools to control cookies and similar technologies, including:
Browser controls to block and delete cookies (look under the heading “Tools”, or similar heading in your particular
browser for information controlling cookies) or third party software installed on your browser.
We may also include tracking code in marketing e-mail messages or our newsletters in order to determine whether
messages have been opened and whether you have clicked on the links in those messages. You may unsubscribe at
any time from these email communications by following the instructions in the footer of the email.
We may from time to time use advertising companies to develop banner ads for our Site. These ads may contain
cookies that may be sent to your browser through the banner ads. We do not have control over cookies placed by
our advertisers, nor do we have access to any information their cookies may collect.
          i.        register to attend DIVERSIFIED trade shows, conferences and events;
          ii.       subscribe to our publications, including e-newsletters;
          iii.      register with our Site;
          iv.       communicate with us by e-mail;
          v.        post comments, ratings or messages to any of our chat groups, bulletin boards or forums;
                    and/or complete online forms, surveys or contest entries.
“Personally identifiable information” is information that tells us who you are, such as your name, job title,
company, physical mailing address, e-mail address, telephone and fax numbers and, if applicable, financial
information such as your credit card information. We may collect this information when you:
You always have the option not to provide the personal information we request. If you choose not to provide the
personal information we request, you can still visit our Site, but you may be unable to access or use certain options
and/or services.
Use and Disclosure of Personal and Financial Information
If you elect to provide personal information to us, we may use it for the purpose for which it was provided (e.g., to
establish your account, send you publications to which you have subscribed, attribute content you submit to the
Site to you, etc.), and for the other purposes set forth herein. We may use personally identifiable information to
(1) send you e-mails about your account; (2) respond to e-mails; (3) provide customer support; and (4) perform
other similar functions. We may also use personally identifiable information to send you marketing, advertising
and/or product/service offerings (“Commercial Communications”).
We may share personally identifiable information with our affiliates and with our partners, including our
exhibitors, sponsors and advertisers, for marketing, advertising, and/or product/service offering purposes. While
we will seek to require all such third parties to follow appropriate privacy policies consistent with this Privacy
Policy, and will not authorize them to use this information except for the express purpose for which it is provided,
DIVERSIFIED does not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties.
If you wish to limit the Commercial Communications you receive from us and/or our affiliates and partners, and/or
do not wish to have your personally identifiable information shared with third parties, you may opt (i) not to have
your personally identifiable information shared with third parties, (ii) not to receive Commercial Communications
from third parties, and/or (iii) not to receive Commercial Communications from us except for Commercial
Communications related to the product or service for which you provided your personally identifiable information,
as described below under “Opt-Out Option.”
We may also disclose personally identifiable information in special cases when we have reason to believe that
disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may have
breached our Terms of Use, or who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or
                                                                           © 2015 Diversified Communications

unintentionally) our rights or property, other users of our Site, or anyone else who could be harmed by such
activities. We may also disclose personally identifiable information when we reasonably believe that the law
requires it.
In addition, as our business changes, we may buy or sell various assets. In the event all or a portion of the assets
owned or controlled by DIVERSIFIED, or any subsidiary or affiliated entity, are sold, assigned, transferred or
acquired by another company, personally identifiable information may be among the transferred assets.
If you submit financial information to us, we may use that information to verify your credit and collect payments
for your purchases, orders, registrations, etc. We may share your financial information with third parties that
process financial transactions on our behalf.
Automatic & Personal Behavior Information
We will use automatic information to personalize our Site based on the preferences you submit to us at the time
you register. We also use the aggregated information to evaluate products and services we may offer to you.
We may use temporary, session-specific cookies to ensure visits to our Site are smooth and customized for the
visitor – for example, to control the display of ads, to track usage patterns on our Site, to deliver editorial content,
and to record registration and personalization information. Cookies allow us to provide a visitor’s browser with
information tailored to the visitor’s preferences and needs. We also may use permanent or persistent cookies that
remain on a visitor’s computer after the visitor leaves our Site.
We may use third party software tools that use your behavior on the site to serve you information that may be of
interest to you. An example of this software is a product called “Evergage.”
In addition, we reserve the right to use the information we collect about your computer, which may at times be
able to identify you, for any lawful business purpose, including to help diagnose problems with our servers, to
gather broad demographic information, and to otherwise administer our Site.
Aggregated Information
We reserve the right to use, transfer, sell, and share aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for
any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.
Information on Children
The Site is a general audience web site. We do not intentionally collect personally identifiable information from
users of this Site who are under the age of thirteen. If we become aware that a user of our web site is under the
age of 13 and has provided any personally identifiable information to us without verification of parental consent,
we will remove that child’s personal information from our files.
Updating Visitor Information
Many of our Site functions (but not all) allow you to correct, update and modify your personal and/or financial
information. If you would like instructions on how you may correct, update and modify your personal and/or
financial information, please contact us at info@divcom.com and provide us with the specific Site through which
you provided information. If you would like to update your information via e-mail, please contact us at
info@divcom.com, and provide us with (1) the name and e-mail address you previously provided to us, and
(2) any updates to your personal and/or financial information.
You may not change your username ID selected at registration for a trade show, event or conference.
Third Party and Affiliated Links
Our Site may from time to time contain links to other websites, including suppliers, advertisers and affiliates. We
have no control over, and are not responsible for, the content of, or information gathered by, these other
                                                                          © 2015 Diversified Communications

websites. We do not endorse any of these websites or the products or services associated with such websites
merely because they are linked to our Site.
Information Posted on Bulletin Boards and Other Forums
Users of our Site should be aware that information you disclose on bulletin boards and other forums may be
collected by others and may result in unsolicited messages from others.
Opt-Out Option
If you do not want DIVERSIFIED to share your personally identifiable information with third parties, or if you do not
wish to receive Commercial Communications from DIVERSIFIED and/or third parties, you may (i) state your
preferences at the time you submit your personal information to us, or (ii) change your preferences at any time by
(a) notifying us in writing (at the Privacy Policy Contact mailing address or email address below) of your e-mail
address and of your preference that we not share your information and/or that you do not wish to receive such
Commercial Communications from DIVERSIFIED and/or third parties, or (b) following the unsubscribe
instructions contained within the e-mail you receive from us.
We will update your preferences as soon as is reasonably practicable.
We will use reasonable efforts to forward your opt-out request (including your e-mail address) to the specific
third-party marketer whose offer you received from us prompting your opt-out or unsubscribe request, so that it
can include your e-mail address on its own do-not-email list. However, even if you opt-out as described above,
we will not be able to remove your personal information from the databases of third parties with which we have
already shared your personal information (i.e., to which we have provided your personal information prior to our
receipt of your opt-out request). DIVERSIFIED does not bear any responsibility for ensuring that any third party
complies with your opt-out or unsubscribe request vis-à-vis its own lists.
Security and Encryption
Unfortunately, information transmitted on the Internet and/or stored on systems attached to the Internet is
not 100% secure. As a result, DIVERSIFIED cannot ensure, warrant or guarantee the security or integrity of such
information.
Privacy Policy Contact
If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us by letter at the address below,
or by e-mail at info@divcom.com
Diversified Communications
121 Free Street Portland,
ME 04101 USA
Attention: Web Master
                                                                          © 2015 Diversified Communications
